weblyest.com 2016-12-03

# Weblyest - Privacy Policy

ArtAutoBusinessCelebritiesCollegeFashionFoodFunnyGamesLifestylePetsRandomSportsTechTravelWeird

**Weblyest.com, is part of the Enigma Media Group, Inc.**  
**In order to help our members clearly understand our data collection and use practices, Enigma Media Group, Inc has decided to follow a standard set of privacy practices and use a standard format to describe our privacy practices.**  
**This privacy policy covers all of the Enigma Media Group, Inc websites.**

Enigma Media Group.com, Enigma respects the privacy of our users and has developed this Privacy Policy to demonstrate its commitment to protecting your privacy. This document is intended to describe for you, as an individual who is a user of Weblyest.com, or our services, the information we collect, how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and your choices about such uses and disclosures.

This Privacy Policy was last updated: March 03, 2013

**Information we may collect about you**

We may collect information that can identify you (personal information), such as your name and email address, (i) when you (or other users) provide it to us when using our website or in some other manner, or (ii) from our business partners, and from other third parties. We may combine the personal information that we receive from different sources.   
We also may collect other types of information in the following ways when you visit our website:

  * Our server logs automatically collect information, such as your IP address, your browser type and language, and the date and time of your visit, which helps us track users' movements around our site and understand trends.
  * We may assign your computer one or more cookies which may collect information to facilitate access to our website and to personalize your online experience.
  * We may use standard Internet tools, such web beacons, which collect information that tracks your use of our website and enables us to customize our services and advertisements.
  * We do not knowingly collect personal information from users under the age of 18.

**Information we collect about you**

In General. We may collect personal information that can identify you such as your name and email address and other information that does not identify you. When you provide personal information through our website, the information may be sent to servers located in the United States and other countries around the world.

  * Information you provide. We may collect and store any personal information you enter on our website or provide to us in some other manner. This includes identifying information, such as your name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number, and, if you transact business with us, financial information such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information). We also may request information about your interests and activities, your gender and age, and other demographic information such as your hometown, your gender or your username.
  * Information from other sources. We may also periodically obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from, business partners, contractors and other third parties and add it to our account information or other information we have collected. Examples of information that we may receive include: updated address information, purchase history, and additional demographic information.
  * Information about others. We may also collect and store personal information about other people that you provide to us, such as their name, address and email address. If you use our website to send others (friends, relatives, colleagues, etc.) a product as a gift, we may store your personal information, and the personal information of each such recipient in order to process those requests or facilitate future activities.
  * Use of cookies and other technologies to collect information. We use various technologies to collect information from your computer and about your activities on our site.
  * Information collected automatically. We automatically collect information from your browser when you visit our website. This information includes your IP address, your browser type and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us, and the referring website address.
  * Cookies. When you visit our website, we may assign your computer one or more cookies, to facilitate access to our site and to personalize your online experience. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our site, such as the web pages you visit, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on our site. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in or use some of the interactive features offered on our website.
  * Other Internet Technologies. We may use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use of our site. We also may include web beacons in advertisements or promotional or other e-mail messages or to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer our website visitors to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming or other activities.

**Information others may collect**

We may allow third-party advertising companies or ad networks to display advertisements on our websites.

  * We do not provide any personal information to these companies.
  * These companies may use tracking tools, such as cookies, to collect information about computers used to view or interact with their advertisements.
  * Some of these companies may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers consumers the ability to opt out of ad targeting by all member companies.
  * If you post information about yourself, and communicate with others using our website, please note that we cannot control who reads your postings or what they do with the information you provide. We encourage you to use extreme caution in posting any personal information.
  * Information collected by third-parties. We may allow third-parties, including our authorized service providers, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies (www.networkadvertising.org).

**How we use the information we collect**

In General. We may use information that we collect about you to:

  * deliver the products and services that you have requested
  * deliver the products and services that you have requested
  * manage your account and provide you with customer support
  * perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others
  * communicate with you by e-mail, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us, our sister IAC companies or other third parties
  * develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our site and other sites
  * verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and sweepstakes
  * enforce our terms and conditions
  * manage our business and perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.
  * 

Financial information. We may use financial information or payment method to process payment for any purchases made on our website, enroll you in the discount, rebate, and other programs in which you elect to participate, to protect against or identify possible fraudulent transactions, and otherwise as needed to manage our business.   
Please review Your choices about collection and use of your information below.

**With whom we share your information**

We will not share your personal information with others except as indicated below, or except when we inform you in advance and give you the opportunity to opt out.   
We want you to understand when and with whom we may share personal or other information we have collected about you or your activities on our web site or while using our services.  
We may share personal information with:

  * Authorized service providers: We may share your personal information, which may include your name and contact information (including email address) with our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include fulfilling orders, providing customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analysis, supporting our website functionality, and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features offered through our website. We may also share your name, contact information and credit card information with our authorized service providers who process credit card payments. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.
  * Business partners: When you make purchases or engage in promotions offered through our website or our services, we may share personal information with the businesses with which we partner to offer you those products, services, promotions, contests and/or sweepstakes. When you elect to engage in a particular merchant's offer or program, you authorize us to provide your email address and other information to that merchant. We will always provide you with the opportunity not to share information with these businesses.
  * Other Situations. We also may disclose your information, including personal information:
  * In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.
  * When we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; or to enforce our website terms and conditions or other agreements or policies.
  * In connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

Any third parties to whom we may disclose personal information may have their own privacy policies which describe how they use and disclose personal information. Those policies will govern use, handling and disclosure of your personal information once we have shared it with those third parties as described in this Privacy Policy. If you want to learn more about their privacy practices, we encourage you to visit the websites of those third parties. These entities or their servers may be located either inside or outside the United States.

Aggregated and non-personal information. We may share aggregated and non-personal information we collect under any of the above circumstances. We may also share it with third parties to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our websites and on websites of third parties. We may combine non-personal information we collect with additional non-personal information collected from other sources. We also may share aggregated information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of visitors to our website and the most popular features or services accessed. This information does not contain any personal information and may be used to develop website content and services

**Your choices**

You may choose:

  * Not to provide any personal information, although that may result in your inability to obtain certain services or use certain features of our website
  * To stop receiving promotional emails from us by sending an email to the contact address at the bottom of this policy or by visiting the Account Settings page associated with your account [link to opt out page(s)]
  * To delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings, although if you do so, some of the features or services of our website may not function properly
  * To review and update your personal information by contacting us at the email address below or, if you have an online account on our website, by logging into that account.

**Security**

We take appropriate physical, electronic, and other security measures to help safeguard personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, or disclosure.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We may occasionally update our Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. If we make material changes in the way we collect, use, or share your personal information, we will notify you by sending you an email to the email address you most recently provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our website.  
that we hope you and other users will find of interest and to target content and advertising. 

**Third-party websites**

There are a number of places on our website where you may click on a link to access other websites that do not operate under this Privacy Policy. For example, if you click on an advertisement on our website, you may be taken to a website that we do not control. These third-party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information, from you and, in some instances, provide us with information about your activities on those websites. We recommend that you consult the privacy statements of all third-party websites you visit by clicking on the privacy link typically located at the bottom of the webpage you are visiting.

**How you can access your information**

If you have an online account with us, you have the ability to review and update your personal information online by logging into your account and clicking on your account settings. You can also review and update your personal information by contacting us at the email address provided below in the How to contact us section of this privacy policy. More information about how to contact us is provided below.  
If you have an online account with us, you also may choose to resign and close your account at any time by visiting the Account Settings page for your account. After you close your account, you will not be able to sign in to our website or access any of your personal information. However, you can open a new, separate account at any time or re-activate your previous account by following instructions we will give you at the time you close your account. If you close your account, we may still retain certain information associated with your account for analytical purposes and recordkeeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, enforce our terms and conditions, take actions we deem necessary to protect the integrity of our web site or our users, or take other actions otherwise permitted by law. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties' policies.

**Your choices about collection and use of your information**

  * You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our website because such information may be required in order for you to register as a member; purchase products or services; participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes; ask a question; or initiate other transactions on our website.
  * At any time you can choose to no longer receive commercial or promotional emails from us by visiting the Account Settings page associated with your account. You will be given the opportunity, in any commercial e-mail that we send to you, to opt out of receiving such messages in the future. It may take up to 10 days for us to process an opt-out request. We may send you other types of transactional and relationship e-mail communications, such as service announcements, administrative notices, and surveys, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. Please note that changing information in your account, or otherwise opting out of receipt of promotional email communications will only affect future activities or communications from us. If we have already provided your information to a third party (such as a service provider) before you have changed your preferences or updated your information, you may have to change you preferences directly with that third party.
  * In certain places on our site we may ask for your phone number. In those places where we ask for your phone number, we will always tell you how your phone number will be used. Only to provide you a service you requested from us. We will not call you for marketing purposes. If you have provided your phone number but no longer wish to be contacted by phone by us, you can visit the Account Settings page associated with your account to let us know your wishes. Please note that we may still need to call you for servicing or other non-marketing purposes.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information-handling practices, or if you would like to request information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes, please contact us by e-mail or postal mail as follows: 

or 

**Enigma Media Group, Inc**

**8335 Sunset Blvd #355**

**West Hollywood, CA 90069**
